ALEJANDRO LÓPEZ BESTEIRO

ng na 1982

www.lopezbesteiro.es

637223576

□ alelopbes@gmail.com

in linkedin.com/in/lopezbesteiro

OVERVIEW

A multidisciplinary designer, with adaptable skills to meet the requirements of any kind of project, whether editorial, corporate, web or mobile services. As a front-end developer, my experience makes me a professional with control over all the developing stages of a digital product.

SKILLS / TOOLS

Photosho						
			Ů			
Illustrator	•	• •	•	•	•	
In Design						
• • •	•	• •	•	•		
Sketch						
• • •	•	• •	•	•		
Invision						
• • •	•	• •	•	•		
Axure						
• • •	•	•				
Premier						
• • •	•	•				
CSS						
• • •	•	•	•	•	•	
HTML						
• • •	•	• •	•	•		
Javascrip						
• • •		•				

Less / Sass

. . . .

Bootstrap

.

WORKING EXPERIENCE

Front end Developer at Knockout Gaming (Málaga)

February 2018 - Present

As part of the front end team, my work involved the organization of CSS architecture and product layout (HTML), as well as serving as a link between the design team for better work optimization between both departments.

UX / Brand Designer at Basebone (Málaga)

June 2013 - February 2018 (4 years and 9 months)

My position switched between brand and UX designer. I was in charge of creating all corporate resources for the company. I developed internal tools from its conceptualization, usability and UX, interface design until its final layout in HTML and CSS, also I maintained the CSS architecture and created style guides for later use of the tech department.

Front end Developer / Grapich Designer at Yoin (Sevilla)

January 2012 - December 2012 (12 months)

Yoin pretended to be a micropayment application through mobile platforms, was developed enterely in web language. I was part of the design group, helping to create the graphic and development material and the one in charge of the front-end of the project.

Web and Graphic Designer at i2Factory (Huelva)

February 2011 - August 2011 (7 months)

My work, as a freelance, for this technology company involved the creation of graphic and interactive projects. Taking part in projects such as the creation of a mobile application for the Latin American Film Festival of Huelva.

Advertising Department at Onda Local de Andalucia (Huelva)

July 2010 - September 2010 (3 months)

Internship in OLA (Onda Local de Andalucía) in the advertising department performing tasks concerning the design and development of campaigns.

Graphic Designer and Layout Designer at Sogel Magazine (Sevilla)

June 2010 - July 2010 (2 months)

I was in charge of the design and layout of the first issue of the women's magazine "Sogel". In my internship I carried on with the task assigned previously by that magazine and finished the entire publishing project.

EDUCATION

Master degee in User Experience and Usability by Kschool (Madrid)

November 2016 - April 2017

"Licenciatura en Publicidad y Relaciones Públicas" (Five-year Degree in Advertising and Public Relations) by Universidad de Sevilla

September 2006 - June 2011

Certified Technician in Image /Ciclo Formativo de Grado Superior (a higher education course) by Instituto Pablo Neruda (Huelva)

September 2004 - June 2006

Assistant Technician in Graphic Design, Curso FPO (a course of professional training) organized by FAECA (Seville)

2008 (630 hours)

Digital Photographic Developer, Curso FPO (a course of professional training) organized by Ánfora Formación (Huelva)

2005 (235 hours)

PERSONAL INFORMATION

- High level of spoken and written english.
- Teamwork skills and ability to perform as team leader.
- Knowledge of agile methodologies